analyticsinsight.net 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Analytics Insight

## Privacy Policy

_This Privacy Policy was last modified on September 6, 2017._

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Analytics Insight.

**Copyright**

Analytics Insight is a trademark brand of Stravium Intelligence. Republication or redistribution of content, including by framing or similar means, is prohibited without the prior written consent of Analytics Insight. We value the privacy of our readers. See our privacy policy for complete details

**Information Collection**

While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with information that can be used to contact or identify you. The information may include your name, email address, biographic information, social media handle, social media profile and/or website URL, picture and any other information you choose to provide. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Services.

When you access or use our services, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our website through your computer, we automatically log your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before navigating to our website. In case of mobile, we may also collect your unique device ID, device make and model, device IP address, mobile web browser type and version and mobile carrier. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our website.

**Cookies**

We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our website and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Services. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services.

**Web Beacons**

We may collect information using web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our website or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**Third Party Advertisements**

We may also allow third parties to use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies to collect information about your use of the services. The data collected typically includes information such as your IP address, the browser you use to visit our website, pages viewed and conversion information. This information may be used by Analytics Insight and third parties to, among other things, analyze data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising targeted to your interests and better understand the usage and visitation of our website and other sites tracked by these third parties.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Analytics Insight may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the website. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [Contact Us](http://www.analyticsinsight.net/contact-us/).
